{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.fu..fu.noShow..15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719014448","data":{"timestamp":" 947719014448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719023543","data":{"timestamp":" 947719023543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719023766","data":{"timestamp":" 947719023766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719024729","data":{"timestamp":" 947719024729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719026002","data":{"timestamp":" 947719026002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719028855","data":{"timestamp":" 947719028855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719029698","data":{"timestamp":" 947719029698"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719030011","data":{"timestamp":" 947719030011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719031244","data":{"timestamp":" 947719031244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719034731","data":{"timestamp":" 947719034730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719035714","data":{"timestamp":" 947719035714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719035968","data":{"timestamp":" 947719035968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719036911","data":{"timestamp":" 947719036911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719039713","data":{"timestamp":" 947719039713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719040746","data":{"timestamp":" 947719040746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719041218","data":{"timestamp":" 947719041218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719045721","data":{"timestamp":" 947719045721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719045783","data":{"timestamp":" 947719045783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 79d1d17e-89b4-40b4-9d4e-fac3ebb8243b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719078822","data":{"timestamp":" 947719078821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" c04bc317-f7f4-4836-aa09-3af350617580"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fu_ng'u-fu-su"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719088455","data":{"timestamp":" 947719088455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" c04bc317-f7f4-4836-aa09-3af350617580"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fu_nyu-mchu-fu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719101374","data":{"timestamp":" 947719101374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" c04bc317-f7f4-4836-aa09-3af350617580"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fu_fu-mchu-bu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719108655","data":{"timestamp":" 947719108655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" c04bc317-f7f4-4836-aa09-3af350617580"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fu_chu-fu-mlu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719114653","data":{"timestamp":" 947719114652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" c04bc317-f7f4-4836-aa09-3af350617580"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fu_du-yu-fu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719129152","data":{"timestamp":" 947719129152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" c04bc317-f7f4-4836-aa09-3af350617580"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fu_vyu-fu-shu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719148232","data":{"timestamp":" 947719148232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" c04bc317-f7f4-4836-aa09-3af350617580"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fu_nu-ku-fu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719166738","data":{"timestamp":" 947719166738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" c04bc317-f7f4-4836-aa09-3af350617580"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fu_nju-fu-fu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719184378","data":{"timestamp":" 947719184377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" c04bc317-f7f4-4836-aa09-3af350617580"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fu_mku-mvu-fu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719205638","data":{"timestamp":" 947719205638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" c04bc317-f7f4-4836-aa09-3af350617580"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fu_fu-bu-su"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719211387","data":{"timestamp":" 947719211386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" c04bc317-f7f4-4836-aa09-3af350617580"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_fu..fu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_fu_fu-bu-su"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719230658","data":{"timestamp":" 947719230658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719243379","data":{"timestamp":" 947719243379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719252477","data":{"timestamp":" 947719252477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719264421","data":{"timestamp":" 947719264421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719275586","data":{"timestamp":" 947719275586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719286760","data":{"timestamp":" 947719286760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719303861","data":{"timestamp":" 947719303861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719322767","data":{"timestamp":" 947719322767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719335894","data":{"timestamp":" 947719335894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719346055","data":{"timestamp":" 947719346055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719355962","data":{"timestamp":" 947719355961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719367924","data":{"timestamp":" 947719367924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719376624","data":{"timestamp":" 947719376622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.fa..fu.asc.lc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719388058","data":{"timestamp":" 947719388058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719395490","data":{"timestamp":" 947719395490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.fa..fu.asc.lc.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719403811","data":{"timestamp":" 947719403811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719444199","data":{"timestamp":" 947719444198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719452793","data":{"timestamp":" 947719452793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719460675","data":{"timestamp":" 947719460674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" d2de4707-4f15-42bb-a477-66df82ffb8ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719499618","data":{"timestamp":" 947719499617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_su"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719501325","data":{"timestamp":" 947719501325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_su"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719513468","data":{"timestamp":" 947719513468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719515770","data":{"timestamp":" 947719515770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719523521","data":{"timestamp":" 947719523521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719536807","data":{"timestamp":" 947719536807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ve"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719538699","data":{"timestamp":" 947719538699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ve"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719548611","data":{"timestamp":" 947719548610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719550352","data":{"timestamp":" 947719550352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719568608","data":{"timestamp":" 947719568608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719570593","data":{"timestamp":" 947719570593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719581641","data":{"timestamp":" 947719581641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719583069","data":{"timestamp":" 947719583069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719595919","data":{"timestamp":" 947719595919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719597648","data":{"timestamp":" 947719597648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719607945","data":{"timestamp":" 947719607945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719609556","data":{"timestamp":" 947719609556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_yu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.trc:syl.2ch..2ch..1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719627293","data":{"timestamp":" 947719627293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" 64a87b08-24a7-4e70-b4fe-ae5a82b9c250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.trc_syl.2ch..2ch..1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_yu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719663339","data":{"timestamp":" 947719663339"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" e6c706e6-a2e5-4869-b545-73757fccc7e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719671602","data":{"timestamp":" 947719671601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" e6c706e6-a2e5-4869-b545-73757fccc7e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947719673122","data":{"timestamp":" 947719673122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_021643"," gameId":" e6c706e6-a2e5-4869-b545-73757fccc7e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}